[Music]
[Música]
We're talking about Antonia Vid, who
estamos hablando antonia vid que también
has also denied having anything to do
ha desmentido que tuviera nada que ver
with those photos taken of him
con esas fotos que le hacen a él
leaving Marta's house and Marta
saliendo de la casa de marta y a marta
on the balcony.
sumada en el balcón
[Music]
[Música]
Because you didn't want to give any
porque no has querido dar ninguna
exclusives because I don't want any more. I'm
exclusiva porque no quiero más
determined
determinado
to rethink many things and now I
replanteándome muchas cosas y ahora el
'm the one making the decisions about his life and what I want to do is stop
soy yo y lo que quiero hacer es dejar de
marketing all this and I don't
comercializar con todo esto y no me
feel like
apetece
continuing to feed any of these flavors, but
seguir alimentando nada de sabores pero
you know, they benefited me financially. I haven't
sabes me beneficiaron económicamente no
had any
tengo desde hace ya muchos meses ningún
kind of relationship with Lecturas magazine for many months now. I
tipo de relación con la revista lecturas
have absolutely nothing to do with
no tengo absolutamente nada que ver con
any of that. The other person who
nada de eso a la otra persona que se le
has been pointed out also has nothing to do
ha señalado tampoco tiene nada que ver
with any of that. I know the agency that
con nada de eso se la agencia que lo ha
did it because I already found out who did it
hecho porque ya me enterado de quién lo
and there's also a journalist
ha hecho y también hay una periodista
who has made it very clear that we have
que ha dejado bien claro que no tenemos
absolutely nothing to do with those
absolutamente nada que ver con esas
photographs. At the moment, if you
fotografías para en el momento si te
noticed, no, no, I didn't notice
diste cuenta no no no me di cuenta
because it's public spam. Well, because it
porque sale spam público pues porque
was freezing cold, it was 7 in the
hacía un frío del copón eran las 7 de la
evening on Sunday. When I appear on the
tarde del domingo cuando yo salgo en el
portal, I don't see.  no photographer
portal yo no veo ningún fotógrafo
obviously I can see looking straight ahead in
obviamente se me ve mirando al frente en
front there were 20 cars parked
el frente había 20 coches aparcados
when I was walking
cuando voy caminando
a car passes me I already know who it is
me adelanta un coche ya sé quién es
who the photographer was and I know
quién ha sido el fotógrafo y sé
absolutely everything I will not
absolutamente todo lo que no voy a
consent to them touching my family and
consentir es que toquen a mi familia y
I will defend my daughter
voy a defender a mi hija
until I run out of
hasta que me quede
breath now mine is the mother of
sin aliento ya los míos es la madre de
my daughter has said publicly that she has been
mi hija ha dicho públicamente que se le
greatly harmed on television that
ha hecho mucho daño en televisión eso
she denounced that she is not capable of
que ella denunciaba no es capaz de
making her friends see that they should be a
hacerle ver a sus amigos que sean un
little lenient with her daughter and that she should
poco condescendiente con su hija y que
ask in some way that she not be
pida de alguna manera que no se le haga
harmed so that her daughter does not live the same thing that
daño para que su hija no viva lo mismo
she has lived
que ha vivido ella
and the harm that has been done to her on
y el daño que le han hecho a ella en
television according to what she says it
televisión según cuenta ella
is evident that he and of course
es evidente que el y que por supuesto
Marta riesgo have something to do with the
marta riesgo tengan algo que ver con las
publications of maps as
publicaciones de cartografías como ya
the journalist she refers to already told us in her day,
nos contó en su día la periodista a la
before a vine who is none
que se refiere ante una vid que no es
other than Marisa Martín el azar
otra que marisa martín el azar
[Music]
[Música]